# Project manager & Art director Specialist in Graphic Design, UX, UI & Big Data

Responsible for the communication, development and digital transformation: Corporate Image, Data analysing, Data management, UI, UX, Digital marketing, Graphic design. With the ability to manage international and multicultural teams (15 to 20 people).

#### Etna VILALLONGA MERCADER

Phone: (+33) 783 008 104

Email: etnavm@gmail.com

Date of birth: May 7th, 1988 Taipei. Taiwan

Address: 15 Rue Jean Larrive 69003 Lyon, France

# LANGUAGES

English (native) Catalan (native) Spanish (native) French (spoken)

# English

Français



#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MZ Made for Petite "freelance" Currently (Paris 2017)

High quality shoes for small size women's feet.

TOOL4FOOD Currently (Lyon 2016-2017)

■ B to B services of the agri-food market.

Vennmón 4 years Currently "freelance" (Barcelona 2013-2017)

Society where you can learn languages and its cultures.

MikiBEUMALA "freelance" 1 year (Barcelona 2016)

Contemporary, luxury and unique upholstery.

Bet4talent & Start-teams 1 year "freelance" (Barcelona 2014-16)

Platforms that connects passive technology candidates with specialized firms and entrepreneurs with professionals.

MKT experience: Ruta 1714, MACBA 2 year "freelance" (BCN 2014-16)

Develops cultural & Social Apps for the Government and Museums.

MYWeeboo 2 years "freelance" (US 2014-2015)

US firm specialized in remote technology.

Leonardo Salinas 1 year (Sydney 2014)

Sydney couture wedding gowns.

Tractaments Ekili 3 years (Barcelona 2011-2014)

Quantum physics, light and herbal therapy.

Mercalia Global Market & Recreatic 2 years (Barcelona 2010-2012)

Firm that develops, manages platforms for the stock market and websites for the stock market clients.

Basema Engine, S.L. 1 year "freelance" (Barcelona 2010)

Firm specialized in selling engines parts.

IndoAtlantic 1 year "freelance" (Jakarta 2012)

Exports to the European market equipment for plumbing.

Instituto de Cultura China (ICC) 1 year (Barcelona 2011)

Private school where you learn Chinese and its culture.

Unión Pack less than <1 year (Barcelona 2010)

Firm that develops packaging and banners.

Bassat & Ogilvy <1 year (Barcelona 2009)

An international advertising and communication agency.

Futbolgolf Catalunya 1 year (Girona 2009)

German and Catalan new sport: the union of golf and football.

### LECTURER EXPERIENCE

INSEEC Currently (Lyon 2017)

Ynov and Lim'Art 1 year Currently (Lyon 2016-2017)

Bachelor Teacher

Raffles College of Design & Commerce 2 years (Sydney 2014-2015)

Bachelor & Master Teacher

Karl Von Busse Institute 2 years (Sydney 2014-2015)

Bachelor Teacher

### SKILLS & FIELDS

- PROJECT MANAGER
- **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**
- **CORPORATE IMAGE** 
  - UI & UX
- PHOTO EDITING
  - **PROGRAMER**
- **ILLUSTRATOR**
- **DATA MANAGER**
- LECTURER

### TOOLS

Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator







Lightroom, Soundbooth, Flash







Dreamweaver, Premiere, After Effects









HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript



















Excel, Word, PowerPoint







Sketch, Invision, JustinMind



























### ACADEMIC **QUALIFICATIONS**

2016-2017

INSECC MSc & MBA. Master of Big data, marketing & management RNCP, Bac+5 (Lyon)

2015 (1 year)

**Certificate IV in Training** & Assessment (Sydney)

2014-2015

Raffles College of Design & Commerce, Master of Design Management (Sydney)

2013-2014

Raffles College of Design & Commerce, Bachelor of Design (Sydney)

2008-2010

ELISAVA, School of Design and Engineering, Higher Level. Undergraduate. Graphic Design in Advertising (Barcelona)

2005-2008

CIC Cultural Institution, High School of Arts (Barcelona)

1995-2000

Student at Taiwan **American School** (Taipei)

1993-1995 Student at French International School (Taipei)

# Chef de Projet et Directrice Artistique Spécialisée en conception graphique, UX, UI et Big Data

Responsable de l'ensemble des aspects de la communication et du dévelopment de l'entreprise : Branding, Analyse de données, Gestion des données, UI, UX, Digital Marketing, Graphisme. Gestion des équipes internationales et multiculturelles (15-20 personnes).

#### Etna VILALLONGA MERCADER

Télé: (+33) 783 008 104 Date de naissance : 07 Mai Email: etnavm@gmail.com

Adresse: 15 Rue Jean Larrive 69003 Lyon, France

# LANGUES

Anglais (Maternelle) Catalan (Maternelle) Espagnol (Maternelle) Français (parlé)

# English Français



### EXPÉRIENCE PROFESSIONNELLE

MZ Made for Petite "freelance" Currently (Paris 2017)

Chaussures de haute qualité pour les pieds de petites femmes.

TOOL4FOOD Currently (Lyon 2016-2017)

B to B Services pour la marché agroalimentaire.

Vennmón 3 ans "freelance" Actuellement (Barcelone 2013-2017)

Société d'apprentissage des langues et des cultures.

MikiBEUMALA "freelance" (Barcelone 2016-2017)

Contemporain, luxe et tissus d'ameublement unique.

Start-teams & Bet4talent 2 an "freelance" (Barcelone 2014 -2015)

Plateforme qui meet en relation des candidats tec avec des sociétés et qui relie des entrepreneurs avec des professionnels respectivement.

MKT expérience : Ruta 1714, MACBA 2 ans "freelance" (BCN 2014-16)

Développement culturel et social. Apps pour le gouv. et les musées.

MYWeeboo 2 ans "freelance" (US 2014-2015)

Société américaine spécialisée dans les technologies à distance.

Leonardo Salinas 1 an (Sydney 2014)

Société de couture de robes de mariage hante couture.

Tractaments Ekili 3 ans (Barcelone 2011-2014)

Thérapie de l'énergie quantique, de la lumière et des plantes.

Mercalia Global Market & Recreatic 3 ans (Barcelone 2010-2012)

Développement et gestion de plateformes pour le marché boursier et d'une app et du site web pour marché social.

Basema Engine, S.L. 1 an "freelance" (Barcelone 2010)

■ Entreprise spécialisée dans la vente de pièces de moteurs.

IndoAtlantic 1 an "freelance" (Indonesia 2012)

Exportations vers le marché européen d'équipement pour la plomberie.

Instituto de Cultura China (ICC) 1 an (Barcelone 2011)

École privée d'apprentissage de la langue chinoise et sa culture.

Unión Pack <1 an (Barcelone 2010)

■ Entreprise développant packaging et bannières.

Bassat & Ogilvy <1 an (Barcelone 2009)

Agence de publicité et de communication internationale.

Futbolgolf Catalunya 1 an (Espagne 2009)

Nouveau sport allemand et catalan : L'union du golf et du foot.

# EXPÉRIENCE DE PROFESSEUR

**INSEEC** Actuellement (Lyon 2017)

Professeur de Master

Ynov et Lim'Art Actuellement (Lyon 2016-2017)

■ Professeur de baccalauréat

Raffles College of Design & Commerce 2 ans (Sydney 2014-2015)

Professeur de baccalauréat et Master

Karl Von Busse Institute 2 ans (Sydney 2014-2015)

Professeur de baccalauréat

### COMPÉTENCES **ET DOMAINE**

CHEE DE PRO IET

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

IMAGE CORPORATIVE

UI & UX

RETOUCHE DE PHOTO **PROGRAMMEUR** 

ILLUSTRATEUR

GESTION DE DONNÉES

PROFFSSFUR

#### OUTILS

Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator







Lightroom, Soundbooth, Flash









Dreamweaver, Premiere, After Effects







HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript















Komodo, Responsive, Wordpress







Excel, Word, PowerPoint



Invision, JustinMind, Sketch,







Trello, Basecamp













# DIPLÔMES

2016-2017

**INSECC MSc & MBA** 

MSc de Big data, marketing & management RNCP, Bac+5 (Lyon)

2015 (1 year)

Certificate IV in Training & Assessment: (Sydney)

2014-2015

Raffles College of Design & Commerce

Maitrise en Management de Projets (design, commerce) (Sydney)

2013-2014

Raffles College of **Design & Commerce** Licence en design (Sydney)

2008-2010

ELISAVA École de design et d'ingénierie de BCN B.T.S. en Conception Graphique Publicitaire (Barcelone)

2005-2008

Institution culturelle CIC Lycée. BAC Beaux Arts (Barcelone)

1995-2000

Ecolière à TAS, Taipei American School (Taipei)

1993-1995

Ecolière à l'École Française Internationale (Taipei)